Guide to the United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Photographs, Part I: Negatives PHOTOS.023
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series I. Negatives, Bulk, 1940-1959; 1938-1969 (bulk 1940s-1950s)
  - Subseries I:B - Individuals - 1939-1969
    - Billings - at Airport, Sep 27, 1941 (Negative 774)
    - Bird, Andrew [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27522)
    - Birkett, Clarence [Inquiring Photographer Features], Aug 4, 1948; 1953 (Negative 26765; 27140)
    - Bittlguez, Emil [Photographer Feature], Mar 2, 1949 (Negative 26884-26885)
    - Bivona, Frank [Capsule Biography Feature], Oct 16, 1947 (Negative 27523-27524)
    - Blaker, Gloria [Photographer Feature], Dec 14, 1949 (Negative 27054)
    - Black, Lena [Capsule Biography Feature], Oct 16, 1947 (Negative 27525)
    - Blackwell, Marguerite [Photographer Feature], Oct 29, 1947 (Negative 26635)
    - Blanck, Anna [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27526)
    - Blank, Wae Loti, Aug 16, 1943 (Negative 1512)
    - Blankfein, Seymour [Photographer Feature], Jan 22, 1948 (Negative 26677)
    - Blake, John - 17-Year Woolworth's Worker [Portrait Feature], Aug 7, 1946 (Negative 28543)
    - Blau, Trudy C. [Photographer Feature], Dec 17, 1946 (Negative 26495)
    - Blecher, Harry [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27528)
    - Bleier, Irving [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27529)
    - Blom, Carrie [Photographer Feature], Sep 21, 1944 (Negative 26093)
    - Blook, Danny - Trainee Organizer [Portrait Feature], Mar 10, 1953 (Negative 28953)
    - Bloom and Stark [Portrait Feature], Dec 3, 1945; Jan 7, 1946 (Negative 29527; 28458)
    - Bloom, Edward [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27530-27531)
    - Bloom, Joe [Photographer Feature], Oct 16, 1945 (Negative 26260)
    - Bloomfield, Rose [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27532)
    - Bloomgarden, Helen [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27533)
    - Bloomingdale's - Local 3 Officers [Portrait Feature], Nov 17, 1960 (Negative 29236)
    - Bloomingdale's Committee from Stanford Connecticut Branch Store[Portrait Features], Sep 25, 1956 (Negative 29083)
    - Bloomingdale's Election Interviews, Feb 15, 1950 (Negative 6309-6317)
    - Bloomingdale's Steward(s?) [Portrait Feature], Dec 7, 1949 (Negative 29793-29795)
    - Blour(?), Lottie [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27527)
    - Blum, Eddie [Portrait Feature], Jan 26, 1950 (Negative 28675)
    - Blum, Sylvia [Photographer Feature], Apr 1, 1948 (Negative 26725)
    - Blumberg, Ann - Wage Drive Interview [Portrait Feature], Feb 11, 1952 (Negative 28811)
    - Blumberg, Joan and Dave Blumberg [Photographer Feature], Aug 1, 1951 (Negative 27131)
    - Blumenthal Meeting, Aug 13, 1952 (Negative 9321)
    - Bock, Anton - Elected Steward, Mar 11, 1954 (Negative 12621-12622)
    - Boico, Stan - Optical Department - Rank and File Worker, Mar 19, 1959 (Negative 17189)
    - Bolden, Tommy [Portrait Feature], Jan 8, 1948 (Negative 29463)
    - Bonelli, John [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27534)
    - Bonilla, Danny [Photographer Feature], Oct 16, 1945 (Negative 26262)
    - Bonilla Aids Garcia Family in Sickness Through Medical Plan, Aug 7, 1953 (Negative 11457-11458)
    - Bonilla New Year's Baby, Jan 5, 1953 (Negative 9625-9626)
    - Bonilla, Betty [Portrait Feature], Mar 21, 1946 (Negative 28502-28502)
    - Booker, Grace [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27535)
    - Booker, James - Unemployed Gives to Fighting Fund, Jun 30, 1947 (Negative 3080)
    - Booker, Theresa of Shranz and Bieber [Capsule Biography Feature], Sep 15, 1952 (Negative 27536)
    - Bookman, Nat [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27537)
    - Boone, Larkin and Irvin Rubin - Footwear Division [Photographer Feature], Sep 16, 1946 (Negative 3216)
    - Boracci, Catherine [Photographer Feature], Oct 1, 1948 (Negative 26799)
    - Boras, Betty [Photographer Feature], Jan 18, 1950 (Negative 27065)
    - Borger, Harry [Photographer Feature], Apr 1, 1948 (Negative 26731)
    - Borman, Jack [Portrait Feature], Jun 13, 1949 (Negative 28616)
    - Bortnick, Lynn - Feature on "Miss Inquiring Photographer" in the Union Voice - Reporter with Her Camera and Interviewing Subjects, Mar 31, 1954 (Negative 12737-12747)
    - Bouges [Photographer Feature], Sep 28, 1950 (Negative 27497)
    - Bourk, Lon - One of First Retirees to Receive New Pension Benefits, Jun 1963 (Negative 21836)
    - Bourne, John E. [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27538)
    - Bowe, Altomay [Photographer Feature], Sep 21, 1944; Aug 19, 1947 (Negative '26094; 26588)
    - Bowers, Lonnie [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27539)
    - Boyd, Edward [Photographer Feature], Nov 13, 1945 (Negative 26265)
    - Bradey, Harold Corporal [Portrait Feature], Aug 9, 1945 (Negative 28393)
    - Bradford, Charlie - 1940(?) (Negative 445-446)
    - Bradford, Johanna - Wife of Deceased Lerner Worker Charles Bradford [Portrait Feature], May 7, 1953 (Negative 28965)
    - Bradley, Anna Mae [Photographer Feature], Nov 22, 1944 (Negative 26125)
    - Bradley, Ernest - Interview - Home Interior - Radio, Dec 27, 1941 (Negative 886)
    - Brajevica, Tony [Portrait Feature], Mar 3, 1949 (Negative 28595)
    - Brand, Joan [Photographer Feature], Feb 24, 1954 (Negative 27241)
    - Brandmark, Betty [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27540)
    - Brangman, Lenore [Portrait Feature], Dec 8, 1952 (Negative 28899)
    - Braun, Ethel [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27541)
    - Brayboy, Louis [Photographer Feature], Aug 14, 1950 (Negative 27111)
    - Kornhaber, Sam - Breakstone Steward, Nov 29, 1961 (Negative 19534-19535)
    - Brecher, Harry - Ad-Getter, Jan 30, 1950 (Negative 6147)
    - Brechner, Mar 1961 (Negative 18761)
    - Breen, Bob [Portrait Feature], Oct 2, 1952 (Negative 28877)
    - Brennan, William [Photographer Feature], Jul 22, 1947 (Negative 26572)
    - Bressner, Ben [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27542)
    - Brewer, Don - Hearn's 14 Columnist [Portrait Feature], Feb 26, 1952 (Negative 28818)
    - Bridges, Harry; Harry Bridges at Nightclub, May 29, 1944; Dec 8, 1951 (Negative 1785; 8220-8225)
    - Brier Family Wife Had Polio - Used Medical Plan, Dec 6, 1952 (Negative 10044)
    - Briggs, James (Local 3) [Portrait Features]; In Washington, DC, undated; Sep 15, 1949; Jun 16, 1958 (Negative 25708; 25757; 28622; 29118)
    - Brinka, Jerry - in Uniform, Dec 27, 1941 (Negative 884)
    - British Labor Leaders at 65, Dec 24, 1943 (Negative 1588)
    - Broadcast by Arthur Osman, Oct 26, 1943 (Negative 1554)
    - Broder, Shirley [Photographer Feature], Jul 21, 1954 (Negative 27290)
    - Brodey, Sy Corporal [Portrait Feature], May 25, 1945 (Negative 28357)
    - Brodkin, Hy [Photographer Feature], Nov 12, 1948 (Negative 26817)
    - Brodsky, Betty - Inquiring Photographer; Full Length Portrait [Portrait Feature], Aug 30, 1948; Aug 1959 (Negative 26789-26790; 29170)
    - Brodsky, Morris and Irving Heilig - Beating the Heat at Morris Levinson Shop, Jul 7, 1949 (Negative 5314)
    - Brody, Harold [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27543-27543)
    - Brohnenhaub, Francis - Retiring Lumber Worker and Wife, Jan 5, 1953 (Negative 29857-29857)
    - Bromberg, Tevel - Retirement Party (Miles), Aug 25, 1961 (Negative 19221-19222)
    - Bronx Organizer Candidates, Oct 30, 1942 (Negative 1307)
    - Brooklyn Stewards [Portrait Feature], Nov 14, 1949 (Negative 29791-29792)
    - Brooks Worker Injured - Local 3 AFL, Apr 13, 1946 (Negative 29710-29710)
    - Brooks, Learline [Capsule Biography Feature] [Portrait Feature], undated; Feb 4, 1953 (Negative 27544-27545; 28923-28924)
    - Brounstein, Jan 22, 1948 (Negative 26670-26671)
    - Brown (?), Dorothy [Photographer Feature], May 26, 1947 (Negative 26544)
    - Brown, Al - Leader, Philadelphia District 76 [Capsule Biography Feature]; with Arthur Osman and David Livingston, undated; Jun 27, 1950 (Negative 27546; 6951-6952)
    - Brown, Charles F. [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27547-27547)
    - Brown, Ethel [Photographer Features], Dec 2, 1945; Jan 28, 1954 (Negative 26279; 27235)
    - Brown, Frank [Capsule Biography Features]; Farewell; National Container Statements; [Photographer Feature] [Portrait Features], undated; Jan 1943; Aug 10, 1943; Sep 22, 1945; Dec 17, 1946; Sep 12, 1960; Feb 26, 1962; Jun 1964 (Negative 27548-27549; 25689; 1342-1343; 29708; 2305; 26489; 29225; 29270;29386-29389)
    - Brown, Gail [Photographer Feature], Sep 29, 1947 (Negative 26611)
    - Brown, Harold ["Inquiring Photographer" Features]; [Capsule Biography Feature], Apr 28, 1948; May 18, 1949; undated (Negative 27469; 26953-26954; '27550-27551)
    - Brown, Irma (Mrs. Frank Brown) - Last Day of Work Before Maternity Leave, May 14, 1954 (Negative 12909)
    - Brown, Martin - Blood Donor [Portrait Feature], Apr 18, 1945 (Negative 28343)
    - Brown, Mr. - 65 Headquarters Elevator Operator Retires, Sep 28, 1958 (Negative 16793-16794)
    - Brown, Pauline and Emily Doyle - Retiring Stern's 65'ers, Oct 4, 1956 (Negative 15431-15433)
    - Brown, Roxie [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27552)
    - Brown, Sadka [Capsule Biography Feature] [Portrait Feature], undated; Jan 25, 1950 (Negative 27553-27555; 28674)
    - Brozski, Henry [Photographer Feature], Sep 21, 1949 (Negative 27009)
    - Brugnola, Rita [Photographer Feature], Dec 10, 1953 (Negative 27220)
    - Brumer, Abe [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27556)
    - Brumer, Hilton [Photographer Feature], Nov 26, 1946 (Negative 26463)
    - Bruno, Belle - Elizabeth Taylor Look-a-Like, Apr 6, 1962 (Negative 20050-20052)
    - Brust, Jack [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27557-27567)
    - Bryceland, Sorty - 5 and 10, Aug 13, 1946 (Negative 2251)
    - Bryceland's Kids, Aug 5, 1946 (Negative 29711)
    - Bryne, Daniel, of Worth, Nov 26, 1947 (Negative 3235)
    - Buchbinder, Max [Portrait Feature]; Retiring (with David Livingston and Milton Reverby), Jan 12, 1950; Jul 1, 1958 (Negative 28673; 16626-16626)
    - Buckenberger, John - [Portrait Features], May 14, 1952; Sep 1964 (Negative 28835; 29398)
    - Buckley, Dick [Capsule Biography Feature] [Photographer Feature], undated; Aug 19, 1947 (Negative 27558; 26583)
    - Budman, Ida [Portrait Feature], Jan 31, 1951 (Negative 28754)
    - Budrikias, Joseph [Photographer Feature], Sep 21, 1944 (Negative 26092)
    - Buff, Anne [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27559)
    - Buffet Food Layout for Public Relations (at D. Osman's Wedding), Dec 31, 1952 (Negative 10142-10143)
    - Buonacquista, Antoinette [Photographer Feature], Sep 21, 1949 (Negative 27011)
    - Burch, Willa Mae - of Local 2 [Portrait Feature]; at Sak's 34th Street Service Desk; [Capsule Biography Feature], Dec 20, 1947; 1950; Feb 1951 (Negative 29459; 7393; 27560)
    - Burke, Bob of National Container, Jan 28, 1941 (Negative 489)
    - Burke, Bob on Furlough [Portrait Features]; [Capsule Biography Feature], Mar 4, 1945; Jul 17, 1945; Feb 1951; Sep 9, 1957 (Negative 28328; 28382; 27561-27562; 29101)
    - Burke, John [Photographer Feature], Apr 11, 1950 (Negative 27087)
    - Burke, Bob, Milton Reverby and Nelson Molofsky [Portrait Feature], Feb 24, 1948 (Negative 29467-29468)
    - Burmeister - Sak's 34th Street [Portrait Feature], Sep 12, 1951 (Negative 28777)
    - Burros, Juan [Photographer Feature], Apr 28, 1948 (Negative 27473-27474)
    - Burstein, Sol [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27563)
    - Burton, Blanche [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27568)
    - Burwell, Mattie [Photographer Feature], Oct 13, 1947 (Negative 26613)
    - Buschell, Mollie - Gimbels [Portrait Feature], Apr 12, 1954 (Negative 29044-29045)
    - Busgang, Morris - with Dispatch Card [Portrait Feature], Feb 6, 1959 (Negative 29138)
    - Bush and Kallem, Dec 17, 1945 (Negative 2447-2447)
    - Bush, Harry - in Shoe Market [Capsule Biography Feature], undated; Jun 11, 1943; Dec 15, 1945 (Negative 27564-27566; 29510; 28447)
    - Bush, Lois [Photographer Feature], Nov 19, 1949 (Negative 27036)
    - Bush, Saul [Photographer Feature], Feb 2, 1949 (Negative 26866)
    - Busto, Jesusa of H. A. Enrich - Retiring, Jul 24, 1953 (Negative 11389-11391)
    - Butmankiewiez, Adam [Photographer Feature], Feb 2, 1949 (Negative 26867)
    - Butter, Edward [Photographer Feature], Dec 10, 1946 (Negative 26475)
    - Byrd Konefal, Mary [Photographer Feature], Dec 17, 1946 (Negative 26483)
    - Byrne, John of Hearn's - Irish Football Coach [Portrait Feature], May 7, 1952 (Negative 28834)
    - Caballero, Ralph [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27569)
    - Caesar [Capsule Biography Feature], Apr 1948 (Negative 27596)
    - Cafaro, Anthony F. [Photographer Feature], Apr 11, 1950 (Negative 27093)
    - Cafe Society Interview, May 3, 1946 (Negative 2743-2747)
    - Caldwell, Michael (left) and Barbara Franklin (right)] [Portrait Feature], Apr 8, 1953 (Negative 28961)
    - Calvasa, Ralph [NAMM Worker] and Family at Home; Cooking; at Desk; Son, Bobby; Sons, Bobby and Ralph Jr., Dec 11, 1947 (Negative 3437-3441)
    - Camacho, Joseph [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27570)
    - Camarata, Charles at Work [Photographer Feature]; [Portrait Feature], Dec 17, 1946; May 19, 1947; Apr 23, 1953 (Negative 26497; 3327; 29333)
    - Camp Project: Altures, Mary and Son, George, 1951 (Negative 7754-7760)
    - Campbell, Annie [Photographer Feature], Aug 1944 (Negative 26073)
    - Campbell, Leroy and Herbert -"Camps for Kids" - Kids who Camped Last Year, Apr 8, 1953 (Negative 28959)
    - Candidate's Mug Shots [Portrait Feature], Aug 8, 1960 (Negative 29190)
    - Cannata, Felice [Portrait Feature], Dec 13, 1945; undated; Jun 12, 1945 (Negative 28444; 27571; 26205)
    - Cantero, Lou [Portrait Feature], Nov 29, 1945 (Negative 28439)
    - Cantor, George - President, Credit Union [Portrait Feature], Jan 11, 1944 (Negative 28315)
    - Cantor, Gerald [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27572)
    - Canzano, Josephine [Photographer Feature], undated (Negative 26136)
    - Capaldo, Harriet of Local 2 [Portrait Feature], Apr 1, 1950 (Negative 28679)
    - Capers, Mercedes [Photographer Feature], Aug 8, 1944 (Negative 26068)
    - Capo, Eileen - Applicant, Oct 14, 1961 (Negative 19461-19478)
    - Capone, Harry - Industrial Container Worker and Family, Nov 14, 1947 (Negative 3184-3185; 3230)
    - Carallaro, Roger [Photographer Feature], Oct 11, 1948 (Negative 26809)
    - Carbonell, Ricardo - Local Chairmen - Abe Paley Shoe - Local 2, Dec 5, 1955 (Negative 14482-14482)
    - Cardinali, Diana [Photographer Feature], Feb 20, 1945 (Negative 26160)
    - Careson, John - Chicago, Ill. [Portrait Feature], Oct 1951 (Negative 28792)
    - Carillo, Raymond [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27586)
    - Carlo, Peter [Photographer Feature], Sep 18, 1945 (Negative 26246)
    - Carmichael, Stokely - Freedom Rider, Jul 25, 1961 (Negative 19145)
    - Carnes, Nick [Capsule Biography Feature] [Portrait Features], Aug 23, 1948; Jan 30, 1945; Sep 6, 1955; Jun 16, 1958; Sep 28, 1960; Jun 27, 1962; Sep 9, 1953 (Negative 27573-27584; 28320; 29508; 29115; 29226; 29299-29300; 29007-29008)
    - Carnes, Nick and Family, Aug 8, 1948 (Negative 4434-4437)
    - Carob, Peter [Photographer Feature], Jul 1944 (Negative 26058)
    - Carollo, Felix [Capsule Biography Feature], Aug 23, 1948 (Negative 27585)
    - Carr, Madeline [Photographer Feature], Nov 12, 1946 (Negative 26453)
    - Carrington, Roberta - Member of Times-Columbia Signs Up for Medical Plan Registration, Jul 8, 1957 (Negative 16065-16068)
    - Carter, Elaine [Portrait Feature], Mar 20, 1948 (Negative 29469)
    - Carter, Leroy of Textile [Portrait Feature], Aug 1960 (Negative 29216)
    - Carty, Grayce [Photographer Feature], Jan 1949 (Negative 26847)
    - Casa, Louis [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27587)
    - Casale, Anthony [Photographer Feature], Apr 11, 1950 (Negative 27097)
    - Casdia, Cosimo [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27588)
    - Case, Jack [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27591)
    - Cassano, Margaret [Capsule Biography Feature], Oct 1958 (Negative 27589)
    - Casserio, Frank [Portrait Feature]; Chicago Standard Brands - "That's My Job" [Portrait Feature], Jul 29, 1952 (Negative 28867-28868)
    - Cassone, Dominic [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27590)
    - Castaglio, Nick [Photographer Feature] [Portrait Feature], Jan 28, 1954; Jan 28, 1949 (Negative 27236; 28602)
    - Caswell, Earl [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27592)
    - Catalano, Louise [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27593)
    - Cavanagh, William [Portrait Feature]; Irish Affairs Feature [Portrait Feature]; Organizer [Portrait Feature], Feb 27, 1956; Aug 17, 1960; undated (Negative 28822; 29206; 28843)
    - Cavanaugh, Lieutenant Colonel - Textile Arbitration, Mar 1942 (Negative 1054)
    - Cayton, Revels [Capsule Biography Feature] [Portrait Feature], Apr 1948; Sep 15, 1949 (Negative 27594-27595; 28624-28625)
    - Cegledi, Emma and Daughter - Trenton, NJ [Portrait Feature], Jun 30, 1952 (Negative 28845)
    - Cener, Mac [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27597)
    - Cerullo, Anthony [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27598)
    - Chabala, Michael [Photographer Feature], Mar 2, 1948 (Negative 26698-26699)
    - Chabarek, Anthony [Photographer Feature], Dec 5, 1953 (Negative 27214)
    - Chaisson, Dorothy [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27599)
    - Champagne, Danny [Photographer Feature] [Portrait Feature], Oct 1, 1946; Mar 5, 1957 (Negative 26424; 29092)
    - Chance, Errol on Furlough [Portrait Feature] [Capsule Biography Feature], Jun 7, 1943; Mar 8, 1945; undated (Negative 1478; 28496; 27600)
    - Chaplan, Leo [Portrait Feature] [Capsule Biography Feature], May 18, 1943 (Negative 28247)
    - Chapman, Charles [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27601)
    - Chapman, Morris [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27602)
    - Charleston, Bennett [Capsule Biography Feature], Jul 1, 1952 (Negative 27507)
    - Charnes, Nathan [Photographer Feature], Jan 22, 1948 (Negative 26669-26674)
    - Chasnoff, Esse [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27603Cheli, Al [Photographer Feature] Cheli, Al [Photographer Feature])
    - Cheli, Al [Photographer Feature], Aug 7, 1945 (Negative 26228)
    - Chenry, Joseph [Photographer Feature], Nov 26, 1946 (Negative 26464)
    - Cherry, Frank [Photographer Feature] [Capsule Biography Feature], Apr 20, 1949; undated (Negative 26921-26922; 27604)
    - Cherstein, Maurice [Photographer Feature], Jun 15, 1949 (Negative 26972)
    - Chertok, Morris [Photographer Feature], Apr 2, 1946 (Negative 26332)
    - Chillingworth, Lena [Portrait Features], Oct 21, 1960; Oct 24, 1960 (Negative 29234-29235)
    - Cholost, Dorothy [Photographer Feature], Mar 19, 1945 (Negative 26173)
    - Chomsky, Mildred [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27605)
    - Chrichlow, Ivan [Photographer Feature], Aug 7, 1945 (Negative 26229)
    - Christina, Mary [Photographer Feature], Aug 8, 1944 (Negative 26066)
    - Christmas Feature - Bloomingdale's Worker, 1951 (Negative 8182)
    - Cinuarrion, M. - May Day Marcher, Apr 19, 1949 (Negative 5074-5074)
    - Citti, John - Veteran of Associated Spec. [Portrait Feature], Nov 13, 1945 (Negative 28427)
    - Claps, Frank [Photographer Feature], Jul 14, 1953 (Negative 27160)
    - Clark, June [Photographer Feature], Oct 2, 1953 (Negative 27195)
    - Clarke, Juanita - Hamilton, Ohio [Capsule Biography Feature], Apr 1952 (Negative 27606-27607)
    - Clarke, Rose [Capsule Biography Feature], Apr 1952 (Negative 27608)
    - Classes - Rank and File Teachers [Portrait Feature], Mar 18, 1958 (Negative 29106)
    - Cloran, Helen [Capsule Biography Feature], Apr 1952 (Negative 27609-27609)
    - Cobert, Alfred [Photographer Feature], Jul 8, 1947 (Negative 26566)
    - Cohen, A. - Security Plan Physical Exam Volunteers, Nov 1949 (Negative 5740-5741)
    - Cohen, Abe [Photographer Feature], Apr 1, 1948 (Negative 26720)
    - Cohen, C. - 80th Birthday, Mar 12, 1948 (Negative 29559-29562)
    - Cohen, Charlie - 50 Years in Dry Goods, Jan 5, 1944 (Negative 1600-1601)
    - Cohen, David [Photographer Features] [Capsule Biography Feature]; Wedding; with Caleb Allen [Photographer Feature], Sep 6, 1941; Dec 1942; Sep 3, 1947; Apr 1952, Dec 5, 1952; Sep 7, 1950 (Negative 748-748)
    - Cohen, Dorothea - Committee Stewards UV [Portrait Feature], Sep 15, 1949 (Negative 28626)
    - Cohen, Edwin - Back Pay from Photo Shop, Jul 5, 1945 (Negative 2206)
    - Cohen, Esther [Capsule Biography Feature], Apr 1952 (Negative 27611)
    - Cohen, Ethel [Photographer Feature], Jul 14, 1953 (Negative 27156)
    - Cohen, Fred - Ad-Getter [Portrait Feature], Oct 29, 1943 (Negative 28258)
    - Cohen, Harry [of NAMM] [Portrait Feature], Mar 19, 1947 (Negative 29424)
    - Cohen, Helen [Capsule Biography Features], Apr 1952 (Negative 27612-27613)
    - Cohen, Irving [Capsule Biography Feature], Apr 1952 (Negative 27614-27615)
    - Cohen, Israel [Capsule Biography Feature], Apr 1952 (Negative 27616)
    - Cohen, Jack [Photographer Feature], Oct 29, 1953 (Negative 27208)
    - Cohen, Jack [Photographer Feature], undated (Negative 26078)
    - Cohen, Jack of Arthur Bier - Retirement Party, Feb 28, 1961 (Negative 18752-18753)
    - Cohen, Joe [Portrait Feature], Feb 5, 1946 (Negative 28481)
    - Cohen, Joseph L. [Capsule Biography Feature], Apr 1952 (Negative 27617)
    - Cohen, Lillian L. [Capsule Biography Feature], Apr 1952 (Negative 27618)
    - Cohen, Louis - First Draftee (Korean War) [Portrait Feature], Aug 29, 1950 (Negative 28722)
    - Cohen, Max - Deaf Member [Portrait Feature], Jun 16, 1952 (Negative 28837)
    - Cohen, Muriel [Capsule Biography Feature], Apr 1952 (Negative 27619)
    - Cohen, Nat K. [Portrait Feature], Oct 22, 1945 (Negative 28418)
    - Cohen, Renee [Portrait Feature], Feb 17, 1953 (Negative 28943)
    - Cohen, Renee with Consumer Service Purchases; Renee Cohen with C.S. Purchases; in Customer Service Ad, May 7, 1954 (Negative 12890)
    - Cohen, Sol [Capsule Biography Feature]; and Daughter, Apr 1952; Nov 30, 1953 (Negative 27620; 12091-12092)
    - Cohen, Theresa [Photographer Feature], Nov 13, 1945 (Negative 26264)
    - Cohen, Zeke [Portrait Features], Jun 16, 1958; Jun 14, 1960 (Negative 29121; 29186)
    - Colbert, Mary [Photographer Feature], Mar 19, 1945 (Negative 26174)
    - Cole, James V. [Photographer Feature], Jun 15, 1949 (Negative 26981-26982)
    - Coleman - Local 3 Trainee [Portrait Feature], Aug 30, 1950 (Negative 28725)
    - Coleman, Lewis [Portrait Feature], undated (Negative 29293-29294)
    - Coletti, Mena [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27621)
    - Collazo, Julio - District 65 Art Exhibit Winner, May 1962 (Negative 20156-20157)
    - Collins, William [Photographer Feature], Dec 3, 1946 (Negative 26470)
    - Collura, John Jr. [Photographer Feature], Dec 5, 1953 (Negative 27219)
    - Colon, Eladio [Photographer Feature], 1953 (Negative 27150)
    - Como, Perry - Interview, Mar 1956 (Negative 14723-14753)
    - Condon, Johnny [Portrait Feature], Jul 14, 1947 (Negative 29437)
    - Connolly, E. - Hardware Meeting, Oct 17, 1945 (Negative 29526)
    - Constantino, Virginia [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27622)
    - Consumer Service Feature, 1951 (Negative 8341-8346)
    - Consumers Service Personnel, Dec 5, 1952 (Negative 10043)
    - Contente, Sylvia [Capsule Biography Feature], undated (Negative 27623)
    - Cook, Margaret [Photographer Feature], Apr 27, 1949 (Negative 26947)